Margaret Bourke-White Papers
Margaret Bourke-White Papers
- Photographs, professional
  - LIFE magazine jobs
    - Mt. Wilson Observatory [LIFE Job #650], 1937 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Arctic trip [LIFE Job #651 and 833], 1937 (Box 201, Folder 6-11)
    - Arctic trip [LIFE Job #651 and 833], 1937 (Box 202, Folder 1-7)
    - Arctic trip [LIFE Job #651 and 833], 1937 (Oversize 7, Folder 1)
    - Arctic trip [LIFE Job #651 and 833], 1937 (Oversize 8, Folder 6)
    - Goldwyn Follies [LIFE Job #761], 1949 (Box 202, Folder 7-8)
    - Ft. Peck Dam, Montana [FPD] [LIFE Job #674] (Box 183, Folder 12)
    - Ft. Peck Dam, Montana [FPD] [LIFE Job #674] (Box 184, Folder 1-2)
    - Ft. Peck Dam, Montana [FPD] [LIFE Job #674] (Box 202, Folder 8-12)
    - Ft. Peck Dam, Montana [FPD] [LIFE Job #674] (Oversize 8, Folder 7)
    - Ft. Peck Dam, Montana [FPD] [LIFE Job #674] (Oversize 9, Folder 1-4)
    - Ft. Peck Dam, Montana [FPD] [LIFE Job #674], interpositives 19425-19441 (Box 358)
    - New York slums [LIFE Job #754], 1937-1938 (Box 202, Folder 12)
    - Hollywood sets [LIFE Job #636, 758, and 779], 1937 (Box 202, Folder 12)
    - Hollywood sets [LIFE Job #636, 758, and 779], 1937 (Box 203, Folder 1-2)
    - Jersey City [LIFE Job #1064], 1938-1939 (Box 203, Folder 2-8)
    - Muncie, Indiana [LIFE Job #1246], 1937 (Box 203, Folder 8-12)
    - Muncie, Indiana [LIFE Job #1246], 1937 (Box 215, Folder 7)
    - Muncie, Indiana [LIFE Job #1246], 1937 (Oversize 9, Folder 5-6)
    - S.S. Leviathan [LIFE Job #1244], 1937 (Box 203, Folder 12-13)
    - S.S. Leviathan [LIFE Job #1244], 1937 (Box 204, Folder 1-3)
    - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania [LIFE Job #2342 and 46588], 1956 (Box 204, Folder 3-4)
    - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania [LIFE Job #2342 and 46588], 1956 (Oversize 7, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania [LIFE Job #2342 and 46588], 1956 (Oversize 9, Folder 6)
    - Museum of Natural History [LIFE Job #2498], 1937 (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - United States Assay Office [LIFE Job #2507], 1936 (Box 204, Folder 4-5)
    - James Farley [LIFE Job #2854], 1938 (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - The New South [LIFE Job #30234] (Box 312, Folder 3-4)
    - The New South [LIFE Job #30234] (Oversize 21, Folder 1)
    - Cordell Hull [LIFE Job #3265] (Box 215, Folder 7-8)
    - Cordell Hull [LIFE Job #3265] (Oversize 9, Folder 6)
    - Philharmonic Orchestra [LIFE Job #3312], 1938 (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Hudson River Valley [LIFE Job #4609], 1939 (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - South Shore Power Squadron [LIFE Job #4670], 1957 (Box 204, Folder 5-6)
    - Lambeth Palace [LIFE Job #5330], 1939 (Box 204, Folder 7-8)
    - Winston Churchill [LIFE Job #5394] (Box 215, Folder 8)
    - Winston Churchill [LIFE Job #5394] (Oversize 9, Folder 7)
    - Eton College in Wartime [LIFE Job #5471], 1940 (Box 204, Folder 8-10)
    - Haile Selassie in London [LIFE Job #5468], 1941 (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - London blackout [LIFE Job #5890], 1940 (Box 204, Folder 10-11)
    - General Maxime Weygand [LIFE Job #6193] (Box 215, Folder 8)
    - General Maxime Weygand [LIFE Job #6193] (Oversize 9, Folder 7)
    - Syria [LIFE Job #6208], 1940 (Box 204, Folder 11-12)
    - Egypt [EGY], interpositives 19442, 1940 (Box 369)
    - Chicago elections [LIFE Job #7511], 1940 (Box 204, Folder 12)
    - Chicago elections [LIFE Job #7511], 1940 (Box 205, Folder 1-4)
    - Harry Hopkins in Russia [LIFE Job #9284], 1941 (Box 206, Folder 1-2)
    - Ambassador Laurence Steinhardt [LIFE Job #9539] (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Convoy from Archangel to England [LIFE Job #10103], 1941 (Box 206, Folder 2-4)
    - Shipwreck [LIFE Job #12369], 1943 (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - France, Cuxa[?] [FRC], interpositives 19407-19417, 1950 (Box 358)
    - Religious processions, Cuxa[?] [REL], interpositives 19392-19406 (Box 384)
    - Bach Festival [BMF] [LIFE Job #32234], 1950 (Box 207, Folder 14)
    - Bach Festival [BMF] [LIFE Job #32234], 1950 (Box 208, Folder 1-3)
    - Bach Festival [BMF] [LIFE Job #32234], 1950 (Oversize 10, Folder 1)
    - Bach Festivall [BMF] [LIFE Job #32234], interpositives 19418 (Box 344)
    - Connecticut River Valley [CRV] [LIFE Job #32964], 1950 (Box 208, Folder 3-6)
    - Connecticut River Valley [CRV] [LIFE Job #32964], 1950 (Oversize 10, Folder 1-2)
    - Connecticut River Valley [CRV] [LIFE Job #32964], interpositives 19419-19424, 1950 (Box 348)
    - Strategic Air Command [LIFE Job #33943], 1951 (Box 208, Folder 6-7)
    - Strategic Air Command [LIFE Job #33943], 1951 (Box 215, Folder 9)
    - Strategic Air Command [LIFE Job #33943], 1951 (Oversize 10, Folder 2-4)
    - Strategic Air Command [LIFE Job #33943], 1951 (Oversize 7, Folder 3)
    - America from a helicopter [LIFE Job #35699], 1952 (Box 208, Folder 7-13)
    - America from a helicopter [LIFE Job #35699], 1952 (Box 209, Folder 1-9)
    - America from a helicopter [LIFE Job #35699], 1952 (Box 215, Folder 9-10)
    - America from a helicopter [LIFE Job #35699], 1952 (Oversize 7, Folder 3)
    - America from a helicopter [LIFE Job #35699], 1952 (Oversize 10, Folder 4-8)
    - Free Japan [LIFE Job #36775], 1952 or 1960 (Box 209, Folder 9-13)
    - May Day riots, Tokyo [LIFE Job #36830], 1952 (Box 209, Folder 13)
    - May Day riots, Tokyo [LIFE Job #36830], 1952 (Box 216, Folder 1)
    - May Day riots, Tokyo [LIFE Job #36830], 1952 (Oversize 11, Folder 1)
    - Independence Day, Tokyo [LIFE Job #36867] (Box 209, Folder 13-14)
    - Independence Day, Tokyo [LIFE Job #36867] (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Independence Day, Tokyo [LIFE Job #36867] (Oversize 11, Folder 1)
    - Baby catbirds [LIFE Job #39838] (Box 210, Folder 3-4)
    - TVA Essay [LIFE Job #40825], 1954 (Box 210, Folder 5-6)
    - TVA Essay [LIFE Job #40825], contact sheets and prints (Box 312, Folder 4-9)
    - Colorado dust bowl [LIFE Job #41858], 1954 (Box 210, Folder 6-9)
    - Colorado dust bowl [LIFE Job #41858], 1954 (Box 216, Folder 1)
    - Colorado dust bowl [LIFE Job #41858], 1954 (Oversize 11, Folder 2)
    - N.Y. Thruway [LIFE Job #42497], 1954 (Box 210, Folder 9-10)
    - Busch essay [LIFE Job #43574], 1955 (Box 210, Folder 10-15)
    - Busch essay [LIFE Job #43574], 1955 (Box 211, Folder 1-13)
    - Busch essay [LIFE Job #43574], 1955 (Oversize 11, Folder 3)
    - Connecticut flood [LIFE Job #45787], 1955 (Box 211, Folder 14)
    - Connecticut flood [LIFE Job #45787], 1955 (Box 212, Folder 1-13)
    - Connecticut flood [LIFE Job #45787], 1955 (Box 213, Folder 1-3)
    - Connecticut flood [LIFE Job #45787], 1955 (Oversize 7, Folder 3)
    - Dock strike [LIFE Job #49825], 1956 (Box 213, Folder 3)
    - Wenner-Gren Land [LIFE Job #52051], 1957 (Box 204, Folder 6-7)
    - Various assignments [LIFE Job #6026, 8767, 48702], 1942-1943 (Box 213, Folder 14-15)
    - Various assignments (Box 214, Folder 1-4)
    - Various assignments (Box 216, Folder 1)
    - Various assignments (Oversize 11, Folder 3-4)
  - Book-related work
    Bourke-White published several books, alone and with her husband Erskine Caldwell. Books represented in this subseries include Dear Fatherland, Rest Quietly; North of the Danube; Say Is This the U.S.A.?; They Called It Purple Heart Valley; and You Have Seen Their Faces. Some of these grew out of assignments for LIFE; the LIFE job number is given in brackets, if appropriate.
    - Dear Fatherland, Rest Quietly [DEA]
      See also her World War II photographs, in particular "Faceless Fritz" items as well as Miscellaneous from "Censor" envelope, many of which were used in this book.
      - Dear Fatherland, Rest Quietly, interpositives 2861-2945 (Box 348)
      - Dear Fatherland, Rest Quietly, interpositives 2946-3040; 19515-19627 (Box 349)
    - A Report on the American Jesuits [LIFE Job #39902]
      - Jesuits, 1954 (Box 210, Folder 4-5)
      - The American Jesuits (Box 241, Folder 8-10)
      - The American Jesuits (Box 242, Folder 6-14)
      - The American Jesuits (Box 243, Folder 1-9)
      - The American Jesuits (Oversize 18, Folder 7-10)
      - The American Jesuits (Oversize 19, Folder 1-3)
    - North of the Danube [NOD] [includes LIFE Job #1958, 2444], 1938
      - Chapter 1 - The Roads of Uzhorod (Box 214, Folder 4-6)
      - Chapter 1 - The Roads of Uzhorod (Box 216, Folder 2-3)
      - Chapter 1 - The Roads of Uzhorod (Oversize 11, Folder 5-8)
      - Chapter 2 - Bread in Uzok (Box 216, Folder 3-4)
      - Chapter 2 - Bread in Uzok (Oversize 11, Folder 8-9)
      - Chapter 3 - The Train through the Tatras (Box 216, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 3 - The Train through the Tatras (Oversize 11, Folder 10-11)
      - Chapter 4 - Wine of Surany (Box 214, Folder 6-7)
      - Chapter 4 - Wine of Surany (Box 216, Folder 6-7)
      - Chapter 4 - Wine of Surany (Oversize 11, Folder 11)
      - Chapter 4 - Wine of Surany (Oversize 12, Folder 1)
      - Chapter 5 - Peace in Brno (Box 214, Folder 7-9)
      - Chapter 5 - Peace in Brno (Box 216, Folder 7-8)
      - Chapter 5 - Peace in Brno (Oversize 12, Folder 1-3)
      - Chapter 6 - The Peasants of Dreharovice (Box 214, Folder 9-11)
      - Chapter 6 - The Peasants of Dreharovice (Box 215, Folder 1)
      - Chapter 6 - The Peasants of Dreharovice (Box 216, Folder 8)
      - Chapter 6 - The Peasants of Dreharovice (Oversize 07, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 6 - The Peasants of Dreharovice (Oversize 12, Folder 4-5)
      - Chapter 7 - The Dogs of Ceske Budejovice (Box 216, Folder 8-11)
      - Chapter 7 - The Dogs of Ceske Budejovice (Oversize 12, Folder 5-6)
      - Chapter 8 - Agent in Praha, 1938 (Box 215, Folder 1-6)
      - Chapter 8 - Agent in Praha, 1938 (Box 216, Folder 11)
      - Chapter 8 - Agent in Praha, 1938 (Box 217, Folder 1)
      - Chapter 8 - Agent in Praha, 1938 (Oversize 12, Folder 7-8)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 217, Folder 1-10)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 218, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous (Oversize 12, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous (Oversize 13, Folder 1-3)
      - Miscellaneous [NOD] interpositives 19446-19514 (Box 379)
    - Say is this the U.S.A.? [SAY] [LIFE Job #4499]
      See also Miscellaneous / unidentified: Miscellaneous contact prints, below.
      - Kansas, Utah, Mississipi, South Carolina, 1940 (Box 217, Folder 3-4)
      - Kansas, Iowa, South Dakota, Nebraska, Utah, 1940; includes American Royal Live Stock Show, Maplecrest Farms, Byron Lake (Box 218, Folder 1-15)
      - Utah, Nevada, California, Arizona, 1940 (Box 219, Folder 1-13)
      - Arizona, Texas, Mississippi, Florida, South Carolina, Vermont[?], Illinois[?], 1940 (Box 220, Folder 1-13)
      - Miscellaneous, 1940; [Chicago?], others (Box 221, Folder 1-2)
      - Kansas, Arizona, South Carolina, New York, South Dakota, Mississippi, California, 1940 (Oversize 13, Folder 4-6)
      - Miscellaneous, mostly trains, grain elevators, etc. (Box 311, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 312, Folder 1-3)
      - Miscellaneous [SAY] interpositives 18690-18698 (Box 389)
      - Miscellaneous [SAY] interpositives 19628-19650 (Box 389)
      - Miscellaneous [SAY] interpositives 19651-19689 (Box 390)
    - Shooting the Russian War, See Russia, 1940s below.
    - They Called It Purple Heart Valley [LIFE Job #13949]
      - They Called It Purple Heart Valley (Box 306, Folder 1)
    - You Have Seen Their Faces [LIFE Job #1104; possibly also MBW code YOU]
      See also Miscellaneous / unidentified: Miscellaneous contact prints below.
      - You Have Seen Their Faces (Box 235, Folder 10-15)
      - You Have Seen Their Faces, includes "Westminster, South Carolina" (Box 236, Folder 1-11)
      - You Have Seen Their Faces, includes "Westminster, South Carolina"; signs (Box 237, Folder 1-10)
      - You Have Seen Their Faces, includes signs, L.R.P.B. Church (Box 238, Folder 1-11)
      - You Have Seen Their Faces, includes signs, contact prints, L.R.P.B. Church (Box 239, Folder 1-12)
      - You Have Seen Their Faces, includes contact prints (Box 240, Folder 1-11)
      - You Have Seen Their Faces, contact prints (Box 241, Folder 1-8)
      - You Have Seen Their Faces, contact prints (Box 241, Folder 11-13)
      - You Have Seen Their Faces [includes MBW code YOU 1805], contact prints (Box 242, Folder 1-6)
      - You Have Seen Their Faces, includes "Westminster, South Carolina" (Oversize 17, Folder 9-12)
      - You Have Seen Their Faces, includes "Westminster, South Carolina", signs, L.R.P.B. Church (Oversize 18, Folder 1-6)
      - You Have Seen Their Faces, contact prints (Oversize 19, Folder 5)
      - [MBW code YOU] Interpositives 1597-1801 (Box 399)
      - [MBW code YOU] Interpositives 1802-2352 (Box 400)
      - [MBW code YOU] Interpositives 2353-2860 (Box 401)
  - India
    LIFE magazine sent Bourke-White on assignment to India several times between 1946 and 1951. Rather than filing these by separate job number in the LIFE section, they are grouped here, with additional India photographs which may or may not be related to LIFE jobs.
    - India [LIFE Job #25256], 1948; Pakistan and Jinnah (Box 207, Folder 12)
    - India [LIFE Job #24735], 1947; 1955; mass migration (Box 223, Folder 6-9)
    - India [LIFE Job #24735], 1947; 1955; mass migration (Box 231, Folder 4-11)
    - India [LIFE Job #21238, 24735, 25256], 1946-1948; 1951,; 1955; mass migration; death; famine; Pakistan and Jinnah (Box 232, Folder 1-16)
    - India [LIFE Job #20554, 21087, 21238, 21393, 21433, 21485, 25256], 1946-1948; 1951,; 1960; Pakistan and Jinnah; Jinnah's speech and press conference; Sikhs, Golden Temple and Morcha protest; aftermath of Calcutta riots; Indian politics; famine; caste system; Gandhi's funeral (Box 233, Folder 1-15)
    - India [LIFE Job #21087, 21485, 21592, 25626], 1946-1947; 1951; Gandhi's funeral; aftermath of Calcutta riots; difference between Hindus and Muslims; caste system; temples, scenes, and landscapes (Box 234, Folder 1-17)
    - India [includes LIFE Job #21592], temples and crowds, miscellaneous other (Box 235, Folder 1-10)
    - India [LIFE Job #20554, 21238, 21433, 24735, 25256], 1946-1948; 1951,; 1955; mass migration; death; famine; Pakistan and Jinnah; Jinnah's speech and press conference; Indian politics (Oversize 14, Folder 1-13)
    - India [LIFE Job #20554, 21238], 1951; famine; Indian politics (Oversize 15, Folder 1-8)
    - India [LIFE Job #20554, 21087, 21393, 21485, 21592, 25626], 1946-1947; 1950-1951; Gandhi's funeral; Indian politics; caste system; Sikhs, Golden Temple and Morcha Protest; aftermath of Calcutta riots; difference between Hindus and Muslims (Oversize 16, Folder 1-10)
    - India, temples and crowds, miscellaneous other (Oversize 17, Folder 1-9)
    - Miscellaneous [IDA], interpositives 18158-18209 (Box 364)
    - Miscellaneous [IDA], interpositives 18210-18538 (Box 365)
  - Korea [LIFE Job #37828; 37413]
    Here will be found a small number of photographs of Korea taken on assignment for LIFE magazine. In most cases the job number is unknown.
    - Operation Area in Korea [LIFE Job #37828], 1952 (Box 210, Folder 1-3)
    - Korea, 1952-1953; includes contact sheets (Box 244, Folder 11-14)
    - Korea, 1952-1953 (Box 245, Folder 1)
    - Korea, 1952-1953 (Box 245, Folder 3-4)
    - Korea, 1952-1953 (Oversize 19, Folder 6-9)
    - Korea, 1952-1953 (Oversize 20, Folder 1)
    - Korea, 1952-1953 (Oversize 20, Folder 6)
  - Russia, early 1930s, 1930-1932
    The job number and client for these are unknown. Subjects include Stalin's mother and great aunt, a ballet school, rolling mills, and cities such as Magnetogorsk and Novorossisk.
    - Russia, early 1930s, children's clinic; Colonel Hugh J. Copper (Box 217, Folder 4)
    - Russia, early 1930s, American specialists; assistant photographer; ballet school; children's clinic; Colonel Copper; crowds; Dnieperstroi (Box 221, Folder 2-13)
    - Russia, early 1930s, Dnieperstroi; Kamerny Theatre (Box 222, Folder 1-10)
    - Russia, early 1930s, Kamerny Theatre; Semionova; Dnieperstroi; Magnetogorsk; Stalin's mother and great-aunt (Box 223, Folder 1-6)
    - Russia, early 1930s, Electrazavot (Box 223, Folder 9-11)
    - Russia, early 1930s, Leonid Leonov; Electrazavot; girl conductor from "Eyes on Russia"; Hammer and Sickle Factory; Magnet Mountain; Magnetnaya; Magnetogorsk (Box 224, Folder 1-11)
    - Russia, early 1930s, Magnetogorsk; Novorossisk (Box 225, Folder 1-11)
    - Russia, early 1930s, movie studio; Novorossisk; Moscow nursery; oil wells at Baku; priest; portraits (Box 226, Folder 1-11)
    - Russia, early 1930s, schools; portraits; public buildings; Red October rolling mills; St. Basil's; Kremlin (Box 227, Folder 1-12)
    - Russia, early 1930s, schools; Semionova; Kalil Sodjaia; Stalin's mother and great-aunt; Serebriakov [LIFE Job #67]; shop windows; Russian consulate (Box 228, Folder 1-11)
    - Russia, early 1930s, Stalin's mother and great-aunt; Stalingrad; state farm; Style Institute (Box 229, Folder 1-11)
    - Russia, early 1930s, Tiflis; Tiflis rest home; textiles; types (Box 230, Folder 1-11)
    - Russia, early 1930s, types; tennia player; workers (Box 231, Folder 1-5)
    - Russia, early 1930s, children's clinic; Colonel Hugh J, Copper; Red October rolling mills; Semionova; Stalin's mother and great-aunt; Dnieperstroi; Magnetogorsk (Oversize 13, Folder 5-9)
    - Russia, early 1930s, Stalin's mother and great-aunt (Oversize 14, Folder 1)
  - Russia, 1940s
    Many of these are related to Bourke-White's book Shooting the Russian War. A few are stamped with Life job numbers.
    - Russia [LIFE Job #9172], church scenes and clergy; German POWs; Rear-Admiral G.J.A. Miles; bookstalls; TASS agency and editors (Box 205, Folder 4-13)
    - Russia [LIFE Job #9172], religion museum (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Russia [LIFE Job #9172?], 1953; soldiers drilling (Box 206, Folder 5-7)
    - Russia [LIFE Job #12657], Stalin; tank crew; night bombing of Kremlin (Box 245, Folder 1-2)
    - Russia [LIFE Job #9172], soldiers; tanks; air raid over Kremlin; night bombing; Red Square (Box 245, Folder 4-13)
    - Russia, scenes of daily life; German plane wreckage; bomb damage (Box 246, Folder 1-17)
    - Russia [LIFE Job #9172], Alexander and Orlova in living room (Oversize 7, Folder 2)
    - Russia [LIFE Job #12657], Stalin; Henry Hopkins; Stafford Cripps; night bombing of Kremlin (Oversize 20, Folder 2-5)
  - Russia, interpositives
    - Russia [RUS], interpositives 1-30 (Box 384)
    - Russia [RUS], interpositives 31-359 (Box 385)
    - Russia [RUS], interpositives 360-719 (Box 386)
    - Russia [RUS], interpositives 720-1040 (missing 889) (Box 387)
    - Russia [RUS], interpositives 1041-1500 (missing 1043) (Box 388)
    - Russia [RUS], interpositives 1501-1596 (Box 389)
    - Russia [RUS], interpositives 3193-3311A (Box 389)
    - Russia [RUS], interpositives 15288-15387 (Box 389)
  - South Africa
    Many of these were taken on assignment for LIFE. Subjects include gold and diamond mines and miners, protests against police violence, and women and children. There is some color material.
    - South Africa [LIFE Job #31368, 31650], 1950; 1953; Bechuanaland Protectorate; miners (Box 207, Folder 12-14)
    - South Africa, 1950; Kaiser's nephew, alone and with others (Box 213, Folder 10-14)
    - South Africa [LIFE Job #31650], Kaiser's nephew; miners; workers; woman with child (Box 241, Folder 10-11)
    - South Africa [LIFE Job #31120], gold and diamond mines, miners; "Stop police violence"; includes some contact prints (Box 243, Folder 9-14)
    - South Africa, Kaiser's nephew; scenes of daily life; workers; aerial views; all contact prints (Box 244, Folder 1-11)
    - South Africa [LIFE Job #31368], 1950; 1953; Bechuanaland Protectorate (Oversize 7, Folder 2)
    - South Africa, 1950; Kaiser's nephew in water (Oversize 7, Folder 4)
    - South Africa [LIFE Job #31368, 31650], Kaiser's nephew; gold miners dancing; women (Oversize 19, Folder 3-5)
    - South Africa [SAF], interpositives 19443-19445 (Box 389)
  - World War II
    Perhaps best-known of Bourke-White's photographs are those taken on assignment for LIFE during World War II. Subjects include Allied troops and installations (U.S. Bomber Command in England, WACS in North Africa, French divisions in North Africa, air artillery in Italy, 5th Army at Christmas), individuals (Dwight D. Eisenhower, General T. Roosevelt, the Italian royal family, suicides in Leipzig, the Krupp family), and Buchenwald concentration camp. Material isordered by LIFE Job #, thus roughly chronologically.
    - U.S. Bomber Command in England [LIFE Job #11491] (Box 252, Folder 3-15)
    - U.S. Bomber Command in England [LIFE Job #11491] (Box 253, Folder 1-5)
    - General Eisenhower [LIFE Job #11771] (Box 253, Folder 5-6)
    - Lille raid [LIFE Job #11869], 1942 (Box 253, Folder 6-15)
    - Lille raid [LIFE Job #11869], 1942 (Box 254, Folder 1-4)
    - North Africa [LIFE Job #12385] (Box 206, Folder 4-5)
    - North Africa [LIFE Job #12385], 1943; "Life Boat", others (Box 254, Folder 4-15)
    - North Africa [LIFE Job #12385], "Killed Ones", others (Box 255, Folder 1-15)
    - North Africa [LIFE Job #12385] (Oversize 7, Folder 2)
    - North Africa [LIFE Job #12385], 1943; "Life Boat" (Oversize 21, Folder 5)
    - Horse show at desert airport [LIFE Job #12407] (Box 255, Folder 15)
    - Heavy bombers, main bomb wing [LIFE Job #13532] (Box 206, Folder 8)
    - Naples [LIFE Job #13549], 1944 (Box 206, Folder 9-10)
    - Naples [LIFE Job #13549], 1944 (Box 256, Folder 1-15)
    - Naples [LIFE Job #13549], 1944 (Box 257, Folder 1-15)
    - Naples [LIFE Job #13549], 1944 (Box 258, Folder 1-15)
    - Naples [LIFE Job #13549], 1944 (Box 259, Folder 1-15)
    - Naples [LIFE Job #13549], 1944 (Box 260, Folder 1-15)
    - WACs in North Africa [LIFE Job #13675], 1953 (Box 255, Folder 15)
    - WACs in North Africa [LIFE Job #13675], 1953 (Box 256, Folder 1)
    - Allied Force Headquarters in North Africa [LIFE Job #13745], 1944 (Box 206, Folder 10)
    - Allied Force Headquarters in North Africa and General Spatz [LIFE Job #13745], 1944 (Box 260, Folder 15)
    - Allied Force Headquarters in North Africa and General Spatz [LIFE Job #13745], 1944 (Box 261, Folder 1-15)
    - Allied Force Headquarters in North Africa and General Spatz [LIFE Job #13745], 1944 (Box 262, Folder 1-11)
    - Lend-Lease Equipment of French divisions, North Africa and General T. Roosevelt [LIFE Job #13840], 1943-1944 (Box 262, Folder 11-15)
    - Lend-Lease Equipment of French divisions, North Africa and General T. Roosevelt [LIFE Job #13840], 1943-1944 (Box 263, Folder 1-12)
    - Lend-Lease Equipment of French divisions, North Africa and General T. Roosevelt [LIFE Job #13840], 1943-1944 (Box 264, Folder 1-11)
    - Engineers in Italy [LIFE Job #14122] (Box 206, Folder 10)
    - Engineers in Italy [LIFE Job #14122] (Box 264, Folder 12)
    - Engineers in Italy [LIFE Job #14122] (Box 265, Folder 1-13)
    - Engineers in Italy [LIFE Job #14122] (Box 266, Folder 1-13)
    - Medical Evacuation Unit in Italy [LIFE Job #14241] (Box 206, Folder 10)
    - Medical Evacuation Unit in Italy [LIFE Job #14241], 1944 (Box 266, Folder 13)
    - Medical Evacuation Unit in Italy [LIFE Job #14241], 1944 (Box 267, Folder 1-15)
    - Air artillery Italy [LIFE Job #14264], 1944 (Box 206, Folder 10-12)
    - Air artillery, Italy [LIFE Job #14264], 1944; 1980 (Box 267, Folder 15)
    - Air artillery, Italy [LIFE Job #14264], 1944; 1980 (Box 268, Folder 1-14)
    - Air artillery, Italy [LIFE Job #14264], 1944; 1980 (Box 269, Folder 1-9)
    - Air artillery Italy [LIFE Job #14264], 1944 (Oversize 7, Folder 2)
    - 92nd Division Artillery and Fifth Army [LIFE Job #14264] xxx title and job # mismatch, 92d is 17036; need to check (Oversize 10, Folder 1)
    - Bailey Bridges, Italy [LIFE Job #15330] (Box 269, Folder 9-14)
    - Bailey Bridges, Italy [LIFE Job #15330] (Box 270, Folder 1-10)
    - Aerial pictures of America [LIFE Job #15855], 1944 (Box 206, Folder 12)
    - Aerial pictures of America [LIFE Job #15855], 1944 (Box 270, Folder 10-13)